Malcolm Gomes

Curriculum vitae

OVERVIEW

I am a Masters Computer Science student working on research in the field of artificial intelligence. Throughout my undergrad, I have learned the fundamental concepts of computer science and software engineering.

My current interests are in machine learning, deep learning, computer vision, and artificial intelligence.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JANUARY 2019 - PRESENT

Caev

Full Stack Developer

Developing Full Stack web application for a catering platform.

Using Node.js to work on backend applications. Using React JS to build user interfaces and interactive web pages.

Created Wireframes to design user interfaces for front web application.

May 2019 - September 2019

Ministry of the Solicitor General

Junior Full Stack Developer

Used ASP.NET MVC and MySQL for the backend of a report generation application.

Used JavaScript, jQuery, and Bootstrap to build user interfaces and interactive web pages for the front end of the application.

Worked with a small team to fulfill several requirements through a few sprint iterations.

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JANUARY 2019

Review Board

Front End Web Developer

Used Backbone.js and LESS to improve the user interface and user experience of the Review Board tool

Used the Jasmine framework to create JavaScript unit tests and perform test driven development (TDD). Collaborated with teams to coordinate work on a new interface for an existing web form

MAY 2018 - AUGUST 2018

Justice Technology Solutions

Web Development Assistant

Used PHP and JavaScript to develop new features for existing web applications.

Used WordPress to create and update content on an internal intranet site.

Used Microsoft Word and Visio to create documentation on the use of created web applications and software.

△ | www.github.com/MalcolmGomes

647-677-1449

⊠ malcolm.gomes@ryerson.ca

www.malcolmgomes.com

EDUCATION

2019 - 2021 **Master of Science**

Ryerson University Computer Science

2015 - 2019 Bachelor of Science

RYERSON UNIVERSITY
Major in Computer Science

TECHNICAL SKILLS

LANGUAGES Java, Python, C, C++,

JavaScript

FRONT END HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,

JavaScript, jQuery, React, Redux, Angular, Backbone,

Selenium

BACK END Node.js, Express, Django,

PHP, MySQL, MongoDB

OS GNU/Linux, Windows

DEVELOPMENT Git, GitHub, Visual Studio

LIBRARIES NumPy, SciKit-Learn,

SciKit-Image, OpenCV, Pandas, MatPlotLib, PyTorch,

Tensorflow, Anaconda

INTERESTS

- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning
- Computer Vision
- Data Mining
- Software Engineering
- Full Stack Web Development